[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what planet does Star Wars character Ki-Ai-Mundi die?", "correct_answer": "Mygeeto", "incorrect_answers": ["Geonosis", "Courusaunt", "Dagobah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first message spelled out in a neon sign?", "correct_answer": "Neon", "incorrect_answers": ["Eat at Joes", "The Sahara", "Enter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the group of militia gunmen in the Darfur region of Sudan thought responsible for the serial massacre, rape and forced displacement in 1990 and 2001-2005?", "correct_answer": "Janjaweed", "incorrect_answers": ["Jihad", "Jilbab", "Jintrap"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the prescription reads take 2 IBU 400mg Tab PO BID p.c. disp. q.s. 5 days DAW, how many ibuprofen tablets should be dispensed?", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "30", "40"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which group of ancient people used a system of strings and knots rather than words, to record their history?", "correct_answer": "The Incas", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mayans", "The Edomites", "The Celts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the popular Caesar salad originate?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Spain", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Simbas daughter who is a central character in the Disney film The Lion King II: Simbas Pride.", "correct_answer": "Kiara", "incorrect_answers": ["Nala", "Sarafina", "Sarabi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Venus day, the time it takes Venus to rotate once, is approximately how long?", "correct_answer": "243 Earth days", "incorrect_answers": ["20 Earth hours", "10 Earth hours", "106 Earth days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "St Volodimyr Cathedral, an example of Neo-Byzantine architecture, is located in which Eastern European city?", "correct_answer": "Kiev", "incorrect_answers": ["Sofia", "St Petersburg", "Moscow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following movies are produced by 20th Century Fox. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "House of Wax", "incorrect_answers": ["Me, Myself  Irene", "Dr. Dolittle 2", "Cast Away"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This town, situated in Hawaii County, is the southernmost town in the United States.", "correct_answer": "Naalehu", "incorrect_answers": ["Kamuela", "Mililani", "Pauoa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term refers to a celestial body that resembles a star but does not emit light, because it is too small to ignite internal nuclear fusion.", "correct_answer": "Brown Dwarf", "incorrect_answers": ["Neutron Star", "White Dwarf", "Protostar"]}]